O.k.
now that we've got this set I'm going to go ahead and get the side walls a little damp.
Alright, so picking it up just a little bit; we can keep it nice and thick on top there o.k.
bring it up about right there; let me grab some more clay from the bottom.
It can be a little thinner on the inside but these rims right here; they need to stay nice and fat o.k.
At this point I got the height that I want and there's another things this tools great for; not only is it great for going back putting your mark in, see look a little swirl; alright.
Come in give it that classic casserole body right there; classic o.k. Just like that and then do some wheel trimming here and there's going to be a lot of goop that comes out of the bottom there.
With a form like this I don't like to get it too funky; I like it to be a little civilized.
But that's it right there and you want to go ahead, take this tool; needle, the wire tool nice and flat; and like this out off to the left.
I can tell the thickness on the bottom was perfect because I can see this moving through the bottom, alright.
And then you want to get it off the wheel head; we're going to set it up then we're going to put some ears on it.